{
    "questions": [
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "id": "62373588cfe13103f55eb53f",
            "correctAnswer": "Montenegro",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Yemen",
                "Mexico",
                "Monaco"
            ],
            "question": "Which region of the world uses '.me' at the end of its web addresses?",
            "tags": [],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sport & Leisure",
            "id": "62399eccaf96521963a08708",
            "correctAnswer": "Germany",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Spain",
                "Italy",
                "Argentina"
            ],
            "question": "Which country won the 2014 FIFA World Cup, hosted in Brazil?",
            "tags": [
                "football",
                "soccer",
                "world_cup"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium"
        },
        {
            "category": "Music",
            "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd6c",
            "correctAnswer": "Fatboy Slim",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Basement Jaxx",
                "Chemical Brothers",
                "Daft Punk"
            ],
            "question": "Whose Albums Include \"Better Living By Chemistry\" & \"You've Come A Long Way Baby\"?",
            "tags": [
                "music_albums"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium"
        },
        {
            "category": "Music",
            "id": "625064d0e12f6dec240bdfcf",
            "correctAnswer": "Eddy Grant",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Devo",
                "Suzi Quatro",
                "Nick Gilder"
            ],
            "question": "'Electric Avenue' was a one hit wonder in 1983 by which artist?",
            "tags": [
                "songs",
                "one_hit_wonders"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard"
        },
        {
            "category": "Music",
            "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd88",
            "correctAnswer": "Jenny",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Brenda",
                "Lisa",
                "Julie"
            ],
            "question": "Who Is Tommy Tutone Trying To Call When He Dials \"867 5309\"",
            "tags": [
                "songs",
                "lyrics"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium"
        },
        {
            "category": "Society & Culture",
            "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fcea",
            "correctAnswer": "Indo-European",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Niger–Congo",
                "Dravidian",
                "Kra–Dai"
            ],
            "question": "The language 'Russian' belongs to which language family?",
            "tags": [
                "language"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "medium"
        },
        {
            "category": "Music",
            "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950baa",
            "correctAnswer": "Nine Inch Nails",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "In This Moment",
                "Nitty Gritty Dirt Band",
                "Animal Collective"
            ],
            "question": "Which American industrial rock band released the studio album 'The Downward Spiral'?",
            "tags": [],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard"
        },
        {
            "category": "Sport & Leisure",
            "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9500d8",
            "correctAnswer": "Leeds United",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Chelsea",
                "Newcastle United",
                "Everton"
            ],
            "question": "A Statue Of Billy Bremner Stands Outside The Ground Of Which Football Ground?",
            "tags": [],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard"
        },
        {
            "category": "Film & TV",
            "id": "624dba44de6018633d31f6bc",
            "correctAnswer": "Carly Simon",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Lulu",
                "Nancy Sinatra",
                "Matt Monro"
            ],
            "question": "Who performed the theme song to the James Bond film The Spy Who Loved Me?",
            "tags": [
                "james_bond",
                "film",
                "soundtracks"
            ],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard"
        },
        {
            "category": "Society & Culture",
            "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951c6e",
            "correctAnswer": "The Shepherds",
            "incorrectAnswers": [
                "Three Wise Men",
                "King Herod",
                "The Stable Boy"
            ],
            "question": "According to the bible, who were the baby Jesus's first visitors?",
            "tags": [],
            "type": "Multiple Choice",
            "difficulty": "hard"
        }
    ]
  }